

B.M.D.C.Bandara

Software Engineer Undergraduate

240/B/03, Galahitiyawa, Ganemulla ZIP Code: 11020 Phone: 076-3049683 E-mail: dchamath5@gmail.com

Profile

Highly organized and enthusiastic 23 years old Software Engineer undergraduate with leadership and mentoring skills with hands on experience. A hard worker who is always eager to face new challenges and a seeker of new knowledge and ready to lead in the role being the best.

Academic Qualifications

GCE O/L (Medium: English-2016) Galahitiyawa Central College Ganemulla

Index No: 40532046

English	Α	Buddhism	Α
ICT	В	Business & Acc Studies	В
Sinhala	В	Science	В
Mathematics	С	History	С
English Literature	S	•	

GCE A/L (Medium: English-2019) Private Candidate

Index No: 7628650

Co. Mathematics	С	Chemistry	С
Physics	S	Gen. English	Α
Gen IT	Δ	_	

2nd Year Undergraduate Software Engineering (BSc.SE top up Birmingham City University)

At Java Institute for Advanced Technology

Certificate Programs offered by Sololearn

(Certificate links available on LinkedIn) LinkedIn Account URL: https://www.linkedin.com/in/denuwan-bandara-920a80191/

Experience

Freelancer- Project Associate (9th of November 2021 – 16th of November 2021) Alpha Management Group (Pvt)Ltd.

Completed a software project(Java) as per the request of the company.

GitHub URL: https://github.com/boby-Anchor/siddha.lk-system01/tree/master/small%20bill

Academic Project- Individual Software Assignment (5th of December 2021 – 9th of December 2021)

Completed a standalone Inventory Control System(Java) with an attractive GUI design.

GitHub URL: https://github.com/denam98/inventory control system

Academic Project- Individual Software Assignment (September 2021 – present)

Currently working on a Library management System(Java).

GitHub URL: https://github.com/denam98/library management system

Private Tutor- C language fundamentals & OOP concepts with Java (present)

To Ist and 2nd year undergraduate students of SLIIT.

Programming Language Skills

- High level of competence in applying OOP concepts and in Swing Application Development in Java
- Programming fundamentals of C and C++ languages
- Database Programming with SQL
- Web programming (HTML, CSS, JS, Bootstrap, PHP)
- Basic knowledge on python
 (Currently following 'Programming Essentials in Python' course on Cisco Networking Academy)

Extracurricular Activities

- Junior prefect at school and dhamma school (year 2012 to 2014)
- Secretory of Chess club (Galahitiyawa Central College year 2014)
- President of Junior Buddhists Association (year 2013)
- Member of Western Band (year 2016 & 2017)
- Member of ICT club (year 2016)

Sports:

- Member of school;
 - swimming squad(2013-2016)
 - cricket team(2011 and 2012)

- Member of university;
 - martial arts club(kung fu)(2019-present)
 - paint ball team(2019-present)

Other Interests:

- Hiking
- Debating
- Brainstorming
- Reading

Voluntary Activities

Active member of Rotaract Club of Kadawatha since 2020

Present Community Service Director of Rotaract Club of Kadawatha

Worked with the team of members on several projects.

Conducting support sessions for undergraduate students of Java Institute for Advanced Technology and SLIIT (2020 - present)

C language fundamentals

OOP concepts in Java

Participating for projects organized by Volunteer Sri Lanka.

Personal Information

	Full Name	Bannaka Mudiyanselage Denuwan Chamath Bandara
--	-----------	---

Date of Birth 9th of September 1998

Age 23 years

Sex Male

Nationality Sri Lankan

Marital Status Single

NIC No 982533104v

Declaration

I hereby confirm that the information given above is true and correct to the best of my knowledge.

Date: 30/12/2021 Name: B.M.D.C.Bandara

References

H. A. Lashan Chandika Hettiarachchi

Senior Software Engineer,

Epic Lanka Technologies,

No. 158/1/A, Kaduwela Road, Thalangama, Battaramulla 10120, Sri Lanka.

071-5136975 / 071-6276980

lashan_h@epiclanka.net

Mahesh Herath

Attorney-at-Law, Notary Public,

Unofficial Magistrate & Justice of the Peace,

Commissioner for Oaths

Kadawatha Road,

Ganemulla.

077-6310113

maheshherath 1965@gmail.com